Caio Cerano

São Paulo, São Paulo, Brazil



caiocerano@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/caio-cerano

Summary

You can learn more about me and my work at https://caiocerano.github.io

Front-end developer with 3 years of experience both for web and mobile applications, specialized in creating user and design focused experiences with up-to-date knowledge and technologies.

Specializations

- HTML5/CSS3
- Javascript/Typescript
- React/React Native
- Next.js

Experience



Digital Tech Developer Analyst

Accenture Brasil

Jan 2022 - May 2023 (1 year 5 months)

Developed foundation code of a web application for an internal project.

Fixed bugs and implemented different quality of life features.

Mobile Engineer

Experity - REsight

Dec 2019 - Dec 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Developed a mobile application focused on eCRM.

Education



Universidade Federal do ABC

Bachelor in Computer Science, Mathematics and Computer Science 2018 - 2024



Universidade Federal do ABC

Bachelor in Science and Technology, Generalist with solid background in Exact Sciences

2018 - 2023

🧘 Instituto Federal de Educação, Ciência e Tecnologia de São Paulo - IFSP

Bachelor of Systems Analysis and Development

2017 - 2018

Licenses & Certifications



Autodesk Certified User (ACU) - Autodesk

11.612.977/00011-86

Skills

Node.js • SQL • Material-UI • Serviços Web RESTful • Git • Desenvolvimento de programas • TypeScript • Ciência da computação • Metodologias Agile • Next.js